Register of the O. Edmund Clubb Papers, 1940-1988
Hoover Institution Archives
- SUBJECT FILE, 1956-1983.
  - International League for Human Rights (Folder 2)
  - McGovern for President campaign (Folder 3)
  - Mongolia - Politics and government (Folder 4)
- PHOTOGRAPH, n.d.
  - One print depicting O. Edmund Clubb (Box 25., Folder 5)
- CARD INDEX FILE, n.d.
  - Lecture outlines and research notes, largely concerning Chinese history and politics (Box 26-35.)